Will you reflect on this?
Well, the question is easy ...
It is not so difficult...
This is a very easy question.
We just started, and already stuck
This is not a difficult question at all.
Come on...
Do not waste time ...
Won't you leave now?
Do you have a problem with this question?
And your answer ...
What will you answer?
How about B?
How about A?
Maybe A?
Maybe B?
How about C?
Maybe D?
Maybe it's D?
Even I know the answer ...
Well, everyone knows that ...
So you won’t pick up on the way back
Easy question
What an easy question
Even the hall laughed
Do you know the answer?
Well, one of the first questions
Let's move on!
I know that ... And you?
Well, the question is easy ...
It is not so difficult...
This is a very easy question.
Well it is very easy
And you answer ...
You can already answer
Yes, there are more complicated questions
I do not know what could be here
Here the money is serious ...
This is not 500 dollars for you
Isn't that D?
Maybe B?
How about C?
Maybe D?
Maybe it's D?
Yes, it’s complicated ...
Hard question
Something quite complicated
You need to think well
Will we take risks?
I would not risk it ...
Interest Ask
What answer?
What will you answer?
Do you know the answer?
Do you know the answer?
Well, you can’t know this ...
I see that you do not know ...
Here you need to turn on the head
Try to take a chance!
What a difficult question ...
There is only guessing
Big money is at stake
This is not a joke
No longer laughing, right?
And what is your answer?
And what are you saying?
What is your answer?
This is a difficult question ...
You can use the hints
I would use a hint
For such a case there is a hint
There are clues ...
Would you like a hint?
Hint?
Do you have any clues ...
There are clues ...
Do not take risks - there is a clue
Using a hint?
Ask for help?
It would not hurt to take a hint
The question is complex, take a hint?
Save hints?
The hint would not hurt ...
You have a hint
Well...
I give up...
I have no clue...
